[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0403a_HuntsmanLee",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side01_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side01_01_RecoverSupplies_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0403a_HuntsmanLee",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side01_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side01_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side01_02_NiceFurs_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side02_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side02_01_ObeliskNotes_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side02_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side02_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side02_02_ObeliskDefenders_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side02_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side02_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side02_03_LightBeacons_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side02_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side02_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side02_04_CollectAzoth_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side02_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side02_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side02_05_PlaceSphere_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_06_Amrine",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 25,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0411_0413_d_00_Container_Amrine",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04_Quest_18",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side02_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0413_Amrine_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0411_0413_a_Title",
  "Description": "0411_0413_b_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0411_0413_c_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0411_0413_c_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0411_0413_e_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0411_0413_f_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side02_07_Shattered",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 35,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0411_0414_d_00_container_Shattered",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0411a_WilliamHeron_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04_Quest_19",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04_Quest_18",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0411_0414_Shattered_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0411_0414_a_Title",
  "Description": "0411_0414_b_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0411_0414_c_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0411_0414_c_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0411_0414_e_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0411_0414_f_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0436a_TamraAyad",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side03_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side03_01_RecoverVase_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0436a_TamraAyad_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side03_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side03_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side03_02_AncientScrolls_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0436a_TamraAyad_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side03_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side03_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side03_03_AncientTalismans_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0405a_ArtificerPetrowski_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_01_ScoutCorrupted_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0405a_ArtificerPetrowski_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side04_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_02_PoisonCorrupted_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0403a_HuntsmanLee",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side04_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_03_ToHuntsman_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0405a_ArtificerPetrowski_02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side04_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_04_KillNamed_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0405a_ArtificerPetrowski_02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side04_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_05_GetLocket_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0405a_ArtificerPetrowski_02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side04_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_06_GetFlowers_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0403a_HuntsmanLee",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side04_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side04_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side04_07_ToHuntsman02_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0440a_AtticusDelphi",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side05_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side05_01_ChooseInstrument_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0440a_AtticusDelphi",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side05_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side05_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side05_02_PlayForTown_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0440a_AtticusDelphi",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side05_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side05_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side05_03_EarnAudience_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0443a_OuShen",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side05_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side05_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side05_04_EarnPatron_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0437a_FelixLivius",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side06_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side06_01_DefeatBear_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0403a_HuntsmanLee",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side06_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side06_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side06_02_TownBrag_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0438a_JacobEvans",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side07_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side07_01_GetMead_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0438a_JacobEvans",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side07_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side07_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side07_02_GetWine_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0438a_JacobEvans",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side07_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side07_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side07_03_GetPort_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0410a_BarkeepPolly",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side07_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side07_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side07_04_SaveBar_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0439a_AnwirHughes_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side08_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side08_01_GetReagents_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0439a_AnwirHughes_01",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side08_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side08_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side08_02_SecretIngredient_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0439a_AnwirHughes_02",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side08_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "04A_Side08_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side08_03_DeliverPotions_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0448a_SyndicateAlchemist",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side09_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "04A_Side09_01_LostAlchemy_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "04A_Side10_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_Title",
  "Description": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "04A_Side10_01_CopperSeam_Incomplete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0425_0101_truffles",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 3,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0425_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistEF_Town",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "AchievementId": "S_truffles",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0425_0101_truffles_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "0425_0101_truffles_title",
  "Description": "0425_0101_truffles_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0425_0101_truffles_complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "0430_0101_Arena",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 20,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": false,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "0430_0101_d_00_container_arena",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0430_PVPArena",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "PVPArena_Quest_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "0430_0101_Arena_success",
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Title": "0430_0101_a_Title",
  "Description": "0430_0101_b_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "0430_0101_c_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "0430_0101_c_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "0430_0101_e_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "0430_0101_f_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": true,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": false,
  "Task": "FM_04_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0401_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0401_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0402_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0402_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0403_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0403_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0404_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0404_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0405_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0405_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0406_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0406_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0407_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0407_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0408_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0408_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0410_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0410_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0401_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0401_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0402_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0402_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0403_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0403_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0404_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0404_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0405_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0405_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0406_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0406_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0407_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0407_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0408_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0408_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0410_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0410_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0401_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0401_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0402_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0402_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0403_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0403_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0404_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0404_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0405_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0405_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0406_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0406_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0407_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0407_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0408_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0408_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0410_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0410_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0461_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0461_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0462_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0462_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0463_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0463_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0464_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0464_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0465_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0465_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0467_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0467_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0468_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0468_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0469_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0469_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_0470_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_0470_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0461_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0461_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0462_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0462_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0463_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0463_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0464_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0464_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0465_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0465_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0467_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0467_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0468_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0468_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0469_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0469_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0470_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_S_0470_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0461_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0461_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0462_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0462_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0463_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0463_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0464_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0464_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0465_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0465_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0467_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0467_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0468_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0468_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0469_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0469_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0470_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_C_0470_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_H_01_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_04_H_01_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_H_02_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_04_H_02_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_H_03_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_04_H_03_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_EXP_01a_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_04_EXP_01a_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_EXP_02a_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_04_EXP_02a_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "FM_04_EXP_03a_objective",
  "Type": "Mission",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "FlagPvp": false,
  "CanBeShared": true,
  "CanFastTravel": true,
  "Task": "FM_04_EXP_03a_container",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "Repeatable": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 }
]